<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<view xmlns="http://www.skyve.org/xml/view" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" name="_moreInformation" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.skyve.org/xml/view ../../../../schemas/view.xsd" title="Hello World">
    <form border="true" borderTitle="More information...">
    	<column/>
    	<row>
    		<item>
    			<blurb>
    				<![CDATA[
    				<p><strong>Hello and welcome to Skyve!</strong>
    				<br/>This application has two <em>Modules</em> (represented as two menu sections on the left):
    				<ul>
    					<li><strong>Admin</strong> - a full-function administration module that is included in every Skyve application. Take a moment to look through the features available (that you won't have to build!).</li>
    					<li><strong>Hello World</strong> - this demonstration module.</li>
    				</ul>
    				Skyve has two rendering modes to suit different user agents/device types, responsive mode and single-page-application (also called "desktop" mode). 
    				Skyve applications will (by default) automatically switch to use the most suitable rendering for the user agent or device type it detects.
    				If you are using a laptop or desktop, try the switcher (above right) <i class='fa fa-share-square-o'></i> to switch between the two modes. 
    				The "desktop" mode includes extensive ad-hoc searching, filtering and export capabilities.
    				</p>
    				<p><strong>Making changes</strong>
    				You can make changes to this project:
    				<ul>
    					<li>in Skyve Foundry - to include more <em>Documents</em> and <em>Attributes</em> go back to your project and investigate the <em>Data Design</em> tab, or</li> 
    					<li>in your preferred Integrated Development Environment (IDE) using collaboration via a <em>Git</em> repository - to set this up follow <a href="https://foundry.skyve.org/foundry/?a=e&m=foundry&d=Help#/collaboration">these instructions</a> in the <a href="https://foundry.skyve.org/foundry/?a=e&m=foundry&d=Help#/">Skyve Foundry User Guide</a>.</li>
    				</ul> 
    				</p>
    				<p><strong>Support</strong>
    				<br/>You can create and run your own Skyve applications for free - no matter how many users or modules you use. Skyve applications can be fully customised and branded for your organisation.
    				<br/>If you need help, we offer:
    				<ul>
    					<li><strong>A free trial server</strong> - available so that you can build and try your own applications, or demonstrations like these.</li>
    					<li><strong>Paid hosts</strong> - If you don't want to run or configure your own infrastructure, we provide pre-configured hosts for a low monthly fee.</li>
    					<li><strong>Tailored virtual training</strong> - We can tailor virtual training for you or your organisation.</li>
    					<li><strong>Paid by-the-hour expertise</strong> - Get direct help from one of our Skyve experts to help you design and build the application you need.</li>
    				</ul>
    				For more support options, contact us at <a href="mailto:info@skyve.org">info@skyve.org</a>.
    				</p>
    				<p><strong>Getting started</strong>
    				<br/>To learn how to get started with Skyve, you may like to try:
    				<ul>
    					<li>the <a href="https://skyvers.github.io/Aged-care/">Getting Started Tutorial</a></li>
						<li>the <a href="https://skyvers.github.io/skyve-dev-guide/">Skyve Dev Guide</a></li> 
						<li>our <a href="https://join.slack.com/t/skyveframework/shared_invite/enQtNDMwNTcyNzE0NzI2LTRkMWUxZDBlZmFlMmJkMjQzYWMzYWQxMmQzYWQ1ZTdlODNkNjRlYzVhYjFmMmQ4NTlhYWY4MjNhMGVkZGNlMjY">public Slack channel</a></li>
						<li>the <a href="https://foundry.skyve.org/foundry/?a=e&m=foundry&d=Help#/">Skyve Foundry User Guide</a> (you'll need to be logged into Foundry to access this).</li>
					</ul>
					Or, if you're posting a question to Stack Overflow, use the <strong>skyve</strong> tag so we can find it and respond.
    				</p>
    				<p><strong>Happy Skyving!</strong></p>
    				]]>
    			</blurb>
    		</item>
    	</row>
    </form>
</view>
